This is the third video of the health insurance series in
which we will talk about
how to do cashless treatment. Cashless treatment
means that when you get admitted to the hospital, you do
not have to bear the cost of the treatment, hence you do
not have to pay any co-payment,
your insurance company bears all the expenses.
Now let's talk about how to get it. To get it,
you will have to understand two aspects.
When you get admitted to the hospital, there are
two types of admissions, one is
plan admission and the other is emergency
admission. What is admission? You go to
see the doctor in the OPD, in case you have stomach
ache ward, you get yourself checked, finally he finds out whether
you have a call Redmi
stone or not, then you will have to do this surgery, then he
role plays whether you will
need to do surgery at home, then he
writes your prescription and tells you that admission
for this surgery is plan admission.
What needs to be done for this is that along with this
prescription, you had done your ultrasound, you have to take
a round with them
and dress on duty, you
send all the documents to the health insurance.  It gives
and your processor is done
for initial approval and you get admitted as per the date decided,
before that the insurance company sends you the approval
letter, for this you should
stay in touch with the OTP desk, the second
is magistrate mid-day admission,
what happens is that you do not know that a
student has gone to Tiger this time, aunt has become
dependent on home and you suddenly
go to a hospital and if in that hospital
your friend company has a network hospital
where there is text message benefit, then you
simply Jhumru, I had talked about the documents,
all those documents are there in which
I do red cross admission and
whatever other line of treatment is written,
along with that your details like
your PAN card, your Aadhar card,
your policy document or vaccine card, then
all these documents are for
knife plan admission, friend, for this
mental admission you have to submit it in a special deferred
hospital and then after getting it
signed by a doctor from the rest of India, the
company  They sell it and then
a mark approval comes quickly, people ask this
question, the
hospital had sent a request to your insurance,
this rule of four lakh rupees, so here the 4000 rupees
is just an initial mode in the beginning
just so that you feel that the
process is going well and your treatment can start,
this whole front comes to you at the
time of decision, then you know that your entire bill is prepared, after
preparing it properly, then with Star Sunny,
again your insurance company gets the
details from there, then the final is taken
and after that whatever insurance
actions are there, whether it is capping or
Anmol, it is tweeted properly and the rest
comes from the insurance company,
you have to pay that little amount from your pocket too, if
you liked the information then
if you really liked the information then
like and share it and if you are on the channel for the first time then
definitely subscribe to the channel
but also press the button of this website so that you keep getting such
informative videos on time,
thank you